A Guide to the Philip S. Hench Walter Reed Yellow Fever Collection 1806-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/11/24, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-018)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/11/27, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-019)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/12/01, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-020)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/12/05, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-021)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/12/28, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-022)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1900/12/30, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-023)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/01/08, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-024)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/01/11, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-025)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/01/19, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-026)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/02/02, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-027)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/02/22, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-028)
- TRANSCRIPTION OF LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO HENRY ROSE CARTER 1901/02/26, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-029)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/02/28, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-030)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/03/01, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-031)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/08/20, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-032)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/08/24, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-033)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO WALTER REED 1901/09/01, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-034)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/09/03, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-035)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/09/05, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-036)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/09/06, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-037)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/09/28, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-038)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL [1901]/10/03, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-039)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/10/03, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-040)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/10/06, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-041)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/10/08, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-042)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO JENNIE CARROLL 1901/10/20, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-043)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/10/24, [PHOTOGRAPH AND PHOTOCOPIES] (Box-folder 153-044)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL [1901]/10/26, [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-045)
- THEODORE E. WOODWARD, ET AL, MARYLANDERS DEFEAT PHILADELPHIA: YELLOW FEVER UPDATED (TRANSACTIONS OF THE AMERICAN CLINICAL AND CLIMATOLOGICAL ASSOCIATION, VOL. 87) 1976, REPRINT (Box-folder 153-046)
- THEODORE E. WOODWARD - DESCRIPTION OF CARROLL PAPERS, PRESENTATION TO THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA 1995/02, TNS, TN (Box-folder 153-047)
- LETTER FROM THEODORE E. WOODWARD TO EDWARD HOOK 1995/07/27, ALS (Box-folder 153-048)
- [THEODORE E. WOODWARD] - EXHIBITION CAPTION N.D., TN (Box-folder 153-049)
- CAMP LAZEAR N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-050)
- JAMES CARROLL, MEMORIAL PLAQUE AT THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-051)
- PAINTINGS - CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER BY DEAN CORNWELL - WALTER REED, CARLOS FINLAY, ET AL IN FINLAYS LABORATORY N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-052)
- W. T. COUNCILMAN, PUBLICATIONS ON YELLOW FEVER BY REED AND CARROLL N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-053)
- CARLOS J. FINLAY, ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-054)
- PARAGRAPH OF TEXT FROM HOWARD A. KELLY - WALTER REED AND YELLOW FEVER (BALTIMORE: NORMAN, REMINGTON, 1923), PP. 144, 145 N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-055)
- WALTER REED, JESSE W. LAZEAR N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-056)
- GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG, HENRY ROSE CARTER, COMPOSITE OF WALTER REED, JAMES CARROLL, JESSE W. LAZEAR AND ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE N.D., [PHOTOGRAPH] (Box-folder 153-057)
- WALTER REED IN UNIFORM N.D., PHOTOGRAPH B&W 4.5 X 6.5 (Box-folder 154-001)
- PRESCRIPTIONS WRITTEN BY WALTER REED, SOME AT MYERS & MCCHESNEY, CRAWFORD, NEBRASKA 1883-87, TD WITH AN TRANSCRIPTION COPY (Box-folder 154-002)
- REGISTER OF PATIENTS AT U.S. ARMY POST HOSPITAL, FORT ROBINSON, NEBRASKA FOR 1884 BY WALTER REED 1884, 1 ADS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-003)
- CORRESPONDENCE FROM WALTER REED TO THE FAMILY OF WALTER REED WEAVER 1885, 1886, 1891, 1898, 1944, 4 AlS (COPIES), 4 TRANSCRIPTIONS, 1 PHOTO B&W 8 X 10, 1 NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (COPY) (Box-folder 154-004)
  WEAVER WAS NAMED FOR WALTER REED. A PHOTOGRAPH OF BLOSSOM REED AS A CHILD WAS SENT TO HIM IN REED'S CORRESPONDENCE. AN OBITUARY OF WEAVER IS INCLUDED.
- DEEDS FOR REAL ESTATE IN MARIN COUNTY, FLORIDA 1886/04/09, 1889/03/20, 2 ADS (COPY), 1 AN (Box-folder 154-005)
  WALTER REED AND EMILY REED CONVEYED LAND BACK AND FORTH WITH E. AND A. WARTMAN.
- LETTERS FROM WALTER REED TO THE POST ADJUTANT AT FORT ROBINSON, NEBRASKA 1887/05/21, 1887/06/30, 1 ADS (P), 2 TL (TRANSCRIPTIONS) (Box-folder 154-006)
  RE SANITATION AND THE HOSPITAL REPORT
- REPORT OF THE SURGEON GENERAL OF THE ARMY TO THE SECRETARY OF WAR 1888/06/30, 1893/06/30, 2 TD (COPIES) (Box-folder 154-007)
  INCLUDES REPORTS FROM WALTER REED AT FORT ROBIINSON, NEBRASKA, ORIGINALS AT NATIONAL ARCHIVES
- ANNUAL COMMENCEMENT OF COLUMBIA COLLEGE IN THE CITY OF NEW YORK 1892/06/08, 1 PROGRAM (Box-folder 154-008)
  THE PROGRAM LISTS JESSE WILLIAM LAZEAR AS RECEIVING THE DEGREE OF DOCTOR OF MEDICINE
- "THE RESTRICTION AND PREVENTION OF TUBERCULOSIS" IN "AMERICAN JOURNAL OF HYGIENE AND NUTRITION" 1894/02-07, 1 JOURNAL ARTICLE (COPY) WITH AN (Box-folder 154-009)
  INCLUDES A DISCUSSION BY WALTER F. REED
- "EXAMINATION OF POTOMAC ICE BY THE ARMY MEDICAL MUSEUM" IN "JOURNAL OF THE AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION" (JAMA) 1895/01/19, 1 JOURNAL EXCERPT (COPY) (Box-folder 154-010)
  INCLUDES A LETTER FROM WALTER REED
- REPORT OF FACULTY MEETING OF SURGEON GENERAL'S OFFICE, ARMY MEDICAL MUSEUM 1895/11 - 1895/12, 2 TD (COPIES) (Box-folder 154-011)
  ORIGINALS IN NATIONAL ARCHIVES
- MEDICAL SOCIETY OF THE DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA MINUTE BOOK 1895/11 - 1895/12, 4 TD (COPIES) (Box-folder 154-012)
  INCLUDES SPEECHES OR SUMMARIES BY WALTER REED ON SUBACUTE BACTERIAL ENDOCARDITIS, DIPHTHERIA, AND RABIES. ORIGINALS IN NATIONAL ARCHIVES
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1899/01/31, 1 TDS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-013)
  RE REED'S DUTY AS CURATOR OF THE ARMY MEDICAL MUSEUM
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO MAJOR [B. ALBERT LIEBERMAN] 1899/02/04, 1 TL (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-014)
  RE TYPHOID FEVER
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 91 FROM H.C. CORBIN, ADJUTANT GENERAL 1899/04/19, 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-015)
  REED IS TO REPORT TO CUBA TO DETERMINE CAUSES OF TYPHOID FEVER, RETURN, AND REPORT.
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO S. T. ARMSTRONG 1899/07/10, 1 TLS (Box-folder 154-016)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO [JAMES CARROLL] 18[99]/08/16, 1 TL (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-017)
  REED QUESTIONS WHETHER A TEST HAS BEEN DONE AS REQUESTED AND GIVES FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS FOR EXPERIMENTS..
- PAPERS REGARDING ARTHUR B. HASKINS 1899/09 - 1900/06, ADS (COPIES), TRANSCRIPTIONS, ENVELOPE WITH AN (Box-folder 154-018)
  INCLUDES HASKINS REQUEST TO BE ASSIGNED TO CUBA AND HIS COURT-MARTIAL PROCEEDINGS. WALTER L. REED WAS A MEMBER OF THE COURT. ORIGINALS IN THE NATIONAL ARCHIVES.
- EDITORIAL COMMENT CONCERNING ARTHUR B. HASKINS 05/10 (?), 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-019)
  WALTER LAWRENCE REED WAS A MEMBER OF THE COURT-MARTIAL PROCEEDINGS AGAINST HASKINS. HASKINS DIED IN PRISON, POSSIBLY OF YELLOW FEVER, AND PROVIDED CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE FOR THE MOSQUITO VECTOR FOR YELLOW FEVER.
- STATEMENTS OF ALLOTMENT OF FUNDS FOR PROVINCES IN CUBA AND STATEMENT OF AMOUNTS COLLECTED AND EXPENDED AT THE 16 CUSTOMS HOUSES 1900, 1 TD (Box-folder 154-020)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1900/04/04, 1 TDS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-021)
- LAST WILL AN TESTAMENT OF WALTER REED WITH CERTIFICATE TO VERIFY 1900/06/13, WILL (COPY), CERTIFICATE, SIGNED (Box-folder 154-022)
  REED BEQUEATHS EVERYTHING TO HIS WIFE, EMILY LAWRENCE REED
- DETACHMENT OF THE HOSPITAL CORPS, CAMP COLUMBIA, CUBA 1900/09, 1 TD (COPY) WITH AN (Box-folder 154-023)
  MOST OF THE VOLUNTEERS FOR REED'S EXPERIMENTS ON YELLOW FEVER CAME FROM THIS DETACHMENT.
- EULOGY OF JESSE W. LAZEAR BY CHARLES W. ELIOT, PRESIDENT OF HARVARD UNIVERSITY POST 1900/09/25, AN (Box-folder 154-024)
  "WITH MORE THAN THE COURAGE AND DEVOTION OF A SOLDIER HE RISKED AND LOST HIS LIFE TO SHOW HOW A FEARFUL PESTILENCE IS COMMUNICATED AND HOW ITS RAVAGES MAY BE PREVENTED."
- lETTER FROM WALTER REED TO THE ADJUTANT GENERAL 1900/11/01, 1 TDS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-025)
  RE ADDRESS CHANGE
- SPECIAL ORDERS, NO. 31, H.C. CORBIN, ORDERS FOR JAMES CARROLL 1901/02/06, 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-026)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/07/06, 1 TD (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-027)
  REED MENTIONS STEWARDS [JOHN S.] NEATE AND WILLIAMSON.
- SPECIAL ORDERS, NO. 172, THOMAS WARD, ORDERS FOR JAMES CARROLL 1901/07/25, 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-028)
  ORIGINAL IN THE NATIONAL ARCHIVES
- CONSENT FORM FOR JEREMIAH TOMLINSON 1901/09/05, 1 TD (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-029)
  TOMLINSON CONSENTS TO BE BITTEN BY MOSQUITOES CARRYING YELLOW FEVER. ALSO INCLUDED IS A COMMENT ABOUT MEN ALREADY IMMUNE TO YELLOW FEVER VOLUNTEERING FOR THE EXPERIMENTS TO GET THE MONEY.
- ORDERS FOR JAMES CARROLL 1901/09/30, 1 TELEGRAM (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-030)
- ORDERS FOR JAMES CARROLL EXTRACTED FROM SPECIAL ORDERS 226 1901/10/01, 1 TD (TRANSCRIPTION) (Box-folder 154-031)
- REGISTER OF DEEDS, DAWES COUNTY, CHADRON, NEBRASKA 1904/11/17, 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-032)
  WALTER REED AND EMILY REED CONVEY REAL ESTATE TO GEORGE G. GORTON.
- LETTER FROM JOHN L. CLEM TO MRS. JAMES CARROLL 1913/03/03, 1 TLS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-033)
  RE THE INSCRIPTION OF JAMES CARROLL'S MONUMENT (TOMBSTONE) IN ARLINGTON NATIONAL CEMETERY, INCLUDES AN EXTRACT FROM REGULATIONS REGARDING MONUMENTS AND MARKERS IN NATIONAL CEMETERIES
- LETTERS FROM JAMES C. REED TO SISTER WRIGHT, LETTER FROM LILA REEE 1919/01/04, 1921/09/29, 1951/04/26, 1948/06/08, 2 ALS (P), 2 TL (TRANSCRIPTIONS), 1 ALS, 1 ENVELOPE, 2 AL (TRANSCRIPTIONS), 1 LARGE ENVELOPE, 1 POSTCARD (Box-folder 154-034)
  LETTERS CONCERN THE GRAVE OF JESSE V. REED IN FRANCE (DIED OCTOBER 12, 1918) AND OF HIS REBURIAL IN BLACKSONTE {VA} IN 1921. LILA REED THANKS A[TCHESON] HENCH FOR SENDING COPIES OF THE LETTERS CONCERNING THE BURIAL OF HER COUSIN.
- POSTCARD FROM RONALD ROSS TO MESSRS HENRY YOUNG & SONS, LTD. 1924/02/23, POSTCARD WITH ANS (Box-folder 154-035)
- "WALTER REED" BY G. W. JEFFERS 1935, 1 JOURNAL ARTICLE (P) (Box-folder 154-036)
  REPRINT FROM "FARMVILLE HERALD" DATED MARCH 29, 1935, "YESTERDAY AND TODAY IN THE HEART OF VIRGINIA"
- JOHN J. MORAN'S CERTIFICATE OF RECOGNITION AS A VETERAN 1935/04/05, 1 PRINTED CARD, SIGNED W/ TYPED INFORMATION (Box-folder 154-037)
  CARD IS IN ENGLISH AND SPANISH. DONATED BY PHILIP ULZURRUN
- JOHN J. MORAN'S CERTIFICATE FROM CUBAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL 1935/07/30, 1 TLS (Box-folder 154-038)
  IN SPANISH, DONATED BY PHILIP ULZURRUN
- FIRST DAY OF ISSUE: WALTER REED, "FAMOUS AMERICANS SERIES SCIENTISTS" 1940/04/17, 1 ENVELOPE AND STAMP (Box-folder 154-039)
- LETTERS TO AND FROM FRANCIS L. BERKELEY, CURATOR OF MANUSCRIPTS, UVA LIBRARY 1941 - 1951, 1 AL (TRANSCRIPTION), 3 TLS, 2 TL (COPY), 4 TL (CC), 2 AN (Box-folder 154-040)
  RE WALTER REED AND FAMILY MEMBERS INCLUDING NELLIE REED ELLIOT, MRS. DOUGLAS T. ELAM, LILA REED AND ALICE REED.
- NOTES BY [ATCHESON LAUGHLIN HENCH] 1947/12/01, 1951/06/26, 3 AN (Box-folder 154-041)
  RE RELATIVES OF WALTER REED INCLUDING JAMES REED, LILA REED, LILY BLACKFORD, AND ALICE REED.
- LETTERS FROM JOHN COOK WYLLIE, CURATOR OF RARE BOOKS, UVA LIBRARY TO ATCHESON HENCH 1947/11/14, 1948/03/20, 1952/01/22, 3 TLS WITH AN, 1 TL WITH AN (Box-folder 154-042)
  WYLLIE WRITES ABOUT REED FAMILY MEMBERS INCLUDING MRS. WILLIAM E. GRAVES, ALICE REED, ELIZABETH REED, MARY BLINCOE, JACK DOOLEY REED, TEXIE P. WATTS, MRS. BOWMAN
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN ROSCOE M. WHITE AND ATCHESON HENCH 1948/03, 1 TLS, 1AL (Box-folder 154-043)
  RE LEMUEL S. REED AND J. C. REED AND THE METHODIST CHURCH
- LETTER TO MRS. JOHN J. MORAN FROM HARRY CLEMONS 1951/10/03, 1 TLS (Box-folder 154-044)
  CLEMONS INFORMS MRS. MORAN THAT HER HUSBAND'S MEDAL OF HONOR ARRIVED SAFELY TO THE ALDERMAN LIBRARY AT UVA.
- ARTICLES REGARDING JOHN J. MORAN'S CONGRESSIONAL MEDAL OF HONOR BEING GIVEN TO UVA 1951/10/05, 2 NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 154-045)
- LETTER FROM PHILIP HENCH TO ATCHESON HENCH 1952/01/22, 1 TLS, 1 JOURNAL ARTICLE (Box-folder 154-046)
  HENCH ENCLOSES AN ARTICLE FROM THE "VIRGINIA CAVALCADE" ENTITLED "HOW A REED WAS BENT" FROM WINTER 1951.
- WALTER REED'S HOME IN CHARLOTTESVILLE, VA 1949/11/27, 1953/04, 1959/04/29, 1971/02/02, 1 PAMPHLET WITH AN, 3 AN, 1 NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 154-047)
  PAMPHLET IS TITLED "EARLY CHARLOTTESVILLE ARCHITECTURE"
- "HENCH'S WIFE GIVE LIBRARY FEVER STUDIES" IN "THE CAVALIER DAILY" 1966/09/21, 1 NEWSPAPER CLIPPING, 1 PHOTOCOPY (Box-folder 154-048)
- NEWS RELEASE REGARDING THE GIFT TO UVA OF PHILIP S. HENCH'S COLLECTION ON WALTER REED AND YELLOW FEVER BY HIS WIFE [1966]/09/25, 1 TD (Box-folder 154-049)
- DUNCAN GRONER CORRESPONDENCE WITH EDGAR SHANNON AND MRS. PHILIP HENCH, REMEMBRANCE OF EMILIE (BLOSSOM) REED 1966/10, 1 TD (COPY), 2 TLS (COPIES) (Box-folder 154-050)
  GRONER, A COUSIN OF BLOSSOM, RECOUNTS BLOSSOM'S LIFE.
- "THE STORY OF AN ARCHIVE: CONQUEST OF YELLOW FEVER" IN "MEDICAL TRIBUNE" VOL 7, NO. 129 1966/10/29-30, 1 NEWSPAPER (Box-folder 154-051)
  INCLUDES A PHOTO OF THE VOLUNTEERS
- "DRAMATIC STORY OF YELLOW FEVER BATTLE" IN "MEDICAL WORLD NEWS" 1966/11/11, 1 JOURNAL ARTICLE (COPY) (Box-folder 154-052)
- DEED OF GIFT OF ITEMS FROM THE PHILIP S. HENCH AND MARY KAHLER HENCH YELLOW FEVER COLLECTION GIVEN TO THE UVA LIBRARY BY MARY KAHLER HENCH 1966/12/19, 1 TDS (COPY) (Box-folder 154-053)
- LETTER FROM ELIZABETH REED TO PHILIP S. HENCH 1967/06/05, 1 ALS, 1 ENVELOPE, 1 AN (Box-folder 154-054)
  ELIZABETH IS THE DAUGHTER OF JAMES C. REED, A BROTHER OF WALTER REED.
- "CARLOS FINLAY AND THE CARRIER OF DEATH" BY J. A. DEL REGATO 1968/05, 1 JOURNAL REPRINT SIGNED BY AUTHOR (Box-folder 154-055)
  THIS IS REPRINTED FROM "AMERICAS" MAGAZINE, SIGNED BY DEL REGATO TO MISS ANE FREUDENBERG
- "JAMES L. HANBERRY - DENMARK MAN A NATIONAL HERO" IN "THE TIMES AND DEMOCRAT, ORANGEBURG, S.C. 1969/09/21, 1 NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 154-056)
- "WALTER REED: ARMY SURGEON - BACTERIOLOGIST - EPIDEMIOLOGIST" BY EMMETT B. CARMICHAEL IN THE "ALA. J. MED. SCI" [ALABAMA JOURNAL OF MEDICAL SCIENCES] 1971, 1 JOURNAL ARTICLE (Box-folder 154-057)
- "THE YELLOW JACK" BY WILLIAM M. STRAIGHT AND "THIS IS YELLOW FEVER" BY WILLIAM L. POND FROM THE MEDICAL HISTORY ISSUE OF "J. FLORIDA M. A." [JOURNAL OF THE FLORIDA MEDICAL ASSOCIATION] 1971/08, 2 JOURNAL ARTICLES (Box-folder 154-058)
- "OPEN COLLECTIONS ROCKEFELLER ARCHIVE CENTER" 1979/04, 1 TD (COPY) (Box-folder 154-059)
- OIL SKETCH FOR 'CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER' BY DEAN CORNWELL 1941/ca., PAINTING (Box-folder ON DISPLAY)
- 'CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER' BY DEAN CORNWELL 1941/ca., PRINT (Box-folder VLT.)
  1 OF 10 AUTOGRAPHED ENGRAVER'S PROOFS
- OIL SKETCH FOR 'CONQUERORS OF YELLOW FEVER' BY DEAN CORNWELL 1941/ca., PAINTING (Box-folder ON DISPLAY)
- PHOTOGRAPHS OF 3RD DIVISION HOSPITAL, 3RD NEBRASKA, 3RD NEB. U.S.V. REGIMENTAL REVIEW 1899/03-04, PHOTOGRAPHS (3) (Box-folder OVERSIZE; 1 ON DISPLAY)